Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series XIX. Speeches
  - Speech - SAVMA Educational Symposium - Dinner, 10 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 100)
  - Remarks - Global 2000 Luncheon, 20 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 101)
  - Br. Introduction - Cornell Corporate Forum Luncheon, 23 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 102)
  - Br. Introduction - Cornell Corporate Forum Keynote Speaker, 23 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 102)
  - Remarks - Dinner for Cornell Corporate Forum, 23 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 102)
  - Br. Remarks - Performing Arts Conference, 24 Apr 81 (Box 327, Folder 103)
  - Remarks - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 02 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 104)
  - Remarks - Tower Club Dinner - New York State Theatre - Lincoln Center, 04 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 105)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Westchester County, 08 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 106)
  - Remarks - Senior Staff Briefing, 15 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 107)
  - Speech - Commencement - North Carolina State University at Raleigh, 16 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 108)
  - Remarks - VIP Reception - Class of '57, 22 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 109)
  - Remarks - Law School Convocation, 23 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 109)
  - Br. Remarks - Kroch Luncheon, 26 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 110)
  - Br. Remarks - Business School Conference of the Economic Impact of the Arts, 27 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 111)
  - Br. Remarks - /Introduction - CUMC Commencement, 27 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 112)
  - Remarks - Commissioning Ceremony, 31 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 113)
  - Introduction - Jacqueline Wexler - Baccalaureate Service, 31 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 114)
  - Speech - Commencement, 31 May 81 (Box 327, Folder 115)
  - Br. Remarks - Luncheon for Agway board of Directors, 02 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 01)
  - Br. Remarks - International Hospitality Committee, 03 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 02)
  - Frank Drake Dinner, 03 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 03)
  - Br. Remarks - Community Leaders' Breakfast, 10 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 04)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dedication of Tjaden Hall, 21 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 05)
  - Remarks - Million Dollar Class Ceremony, 12 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 06)
  - Remarks - Reception and Dinner for 50 Year Class, 12 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 07)
  - Remarks - CAA Annual Meeting, 13 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 08)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Binenkorb Center, 13 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 09)
  - Remarks - Reception and Dinner for 25 Year Class, 13 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 10)
  - Br. Thanks - Cornelliana Night, 13 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 11)
  - Br. Remarks - Groundbreaking Ceremony at Arboretum, 16 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 12)
  - Welcome - 26th Annual Service Recognition Dinner, 18 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 13)
  - Speech - Rotary Luncheon, 24 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 14)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dinner for Executive Staff and Deans, 25 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 15)
  - Br. Remarks - Dick Schultz Farewell, 26 Jun 81 (Box 328, Folder 16)
  - Br. toast - On Behalf of Graduates of University of Wales, 18 Jul 81 (Box 328, Folder 17)
  - Remarks - Freshman Convocation, 26 Aug 81 (Box 328, Folder 18)
  - Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation, 28 Aug 81 (Box 328, Folder 19)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Opening Exercises, 01 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 20)
  - Br. Welcome - First Fall Convocation - Sage Chapel, 06 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 21)
  - Br. Remarks - "State of the University" - Presidential Councillors, 09 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 22)
  - Br. Remarks - September "State of the University" - to brief trustees by phone, 09 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 22)
  - Br. Remarks - University Assembly, 24 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 23)
  - Br. Welcome - Freshman Parents' Weekend Reception, 26 Sep 81 (Box 328, Folder 24)
  - Br. Introduction - Lord Ashby's Lecture #1, 05 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 25)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of James Baker Institute, 09 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 26)
  - Speech - Central Association of OB/GYN Meeting - "Cos, Cnidos and CAOG", 15 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 27-29)
  - Remarks - Dedication of Submicron Facility, 16 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 30)
  - Br. Remarks - Engineering Dinner, 16 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 31)
  - Remarks - Reception and Dinner with Venezuelan Visitors, 23 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 32)
  - Speech - "State of the University" - Trustee/Council Weekend, 30 Oct 81 (Box 328, Folder 33)
  - Br. Remarks - Fund Raising for University Concert Series [removed], 12 Nov 81 (Box 328, Folder 34)
  - Br. Remarks - Corporate Liaison Committee, 13 Nov 81 (Box 328, Folder 35)
  - Br. Remarks - Weiss Group from CUMC, 14 Nov 81 (Box 328, Folder 36)
  - New Trustees Orientation, 01 Dec 81 (Box 328, Folder 37)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Ithaca, 07 Dec 81 (Box 328, Folder 38)
  - Speech - Annual Co-op Extension Conference - Grossingers, 11 Nov 81 (Box 328, Folder 39)
  - Br. Remarks - Mayor Bordoni's Farewell (Raymond Bordoni, Jr.), 30 Dec 81 (Box 328, Folder 40)
  - Speech - Convocation in San Francisco, 10 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 41)
  - Br. Remarks - Q& A - Honolulu Rotary Club, 12 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 42)
  - Speech - Honolulu Alumni Dinner, 12 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 42)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornell Applicant Reception - Hawaii, 13 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 43)
  - Speech - "A cornell Perspective on Common Learning", 23 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 44-45)
  - Br. Remarks - Public Affairs Workshop, 26 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 46)
  - Remarks - New Trustee Orientation, 28 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 47)
  - Br. Remarks - Major Gifts Committee, 28 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 47)
  - Remarks - CU Association of Class Officers, 30 Jan 82 (Box 328, Folder 48)
  - Closing Remarks - Planning Session with B& PA (Business and Public Administration) Major Donors, 04 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 49)
  - Toast - Dinner with B& PA Major Donors, 04 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 49)
  - Remarks - Alumni Dinner Atlanta, 09 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 50)
  - Speech - Alumni - Sarasota, Florida, 11 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 51)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Ft. Lauderdale, Florida, 12 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 52)
  - Speech - Ocean Club Luncheon - Florida, 15 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 53)
  - Speech - Alumni Luncheon - Florida [removed], 16 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 54)
  - Speech - Commemoration Day Exercises - Johns Hopkins, 22 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 55)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Meting with IFC Presidents, 24 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 56)
  - Remarks - Financial Aid Forum, 26 Feb 82 (Box 328, Folder 57)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Boston, 01 Mar 82 (Box 328, Folder 58)
  - Vr. Br. Remarks - Employee Brown Bag Lunch, 05 Mar 82 (Box 328, Folder 59)
  - Vr. Br. Remarks - VIP Visitors (Engineering), 19 Mar 82 (Box 328, Folder 60)
  - Remarks - IBM Press Conference NYC, 30 Mar 82 (Box 328, Folder 61)
  - Remarks - Uris Eulogy, 30 Mar 82 (Box 328, Folder 62)
  - Vr. Br. Remarks - Dinner in Honor of Edwin KcKee, 05 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 63)
  - Br. Introduction - Luncheon for Hatfield Fellow - Roger B. Smith, 07 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 64)
  - Br. Introduction - Hatfield Fellow Address by Roger B. Smith, 07 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 64)
  - Presentation - Hatfield Fellow Award to Roger B. Smith, 07 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 64)
  - Interview - Malott Times, 16 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 65)
  - Br. Remarks - Panel - Scientific Communication and National Security - National Academy of Science, 17 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 66)
  - Remarks - Wagner College Inauguration, 23 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 67)
  - Remarks - Tower Club Dinner, 27 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 68)
  - V. Br. Remarks - VIP Reception, 30 Apr 82 (Box 328, Folder 69)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Mort Adams Testimonial Dinner, 01 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 70)
  - Speech - Commencement - University of Nevada, 23 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 71)
  - Remarks - Human Ecology Faculty Workshop - "Common Learning", 25 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 72)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornell Medical College Commencement, 26 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 73)
  - Remarks - Commissioning Ceremony, 30 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 74)
  - Introduce - Sol Linowitz - Baccalaureate Service, 30 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 75)
  - Speech - Cornell Commencement, 30 May 82 (Box 328, Folder 76)
  - Remarks - Employee Assembly, 01 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 77)
  - Br. Welcome - Middle Management Seminar, 01 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 78)
  - Commentator - ACUSNY Meeting at Rensselaerville, 08 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 79)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Library Associates Dinner, 10 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 80)
  - Remarks - Dedication of Floyd Newman Arboretum, 10 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 81)
  - Remarks - Dedication of Robert Purcell Union, 11 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 82)
  - Br. Remarks - Million Dollar Class, 11 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 83)
  - Br. Remarks - 50th Reunion Dinner, 11 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 84)
  - Speech - Cornell alumni Association Annual Meeting - State of the U., 12 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 85)
  - Br. Remarks - 25th Reunion Dinner, 12 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 86)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornelliana Night, 12 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 87)
  - Br. Remarks - 27th Annual Service Recognition Dinner, 14 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 88)
  - V. Br. Remarks - AAB & VC (Arecibo Advisory Board and Visiting Committee) Dinner - Benn Conger Inn, 17 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 89)
  - Br. Welcome - 9th National Congress of Applied Mechanics, 21 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 90)
  - Presentation - Business Advisory Council, 25 Jun 82 (Box 328, Folder 91)
  - Br. Welcome - 100th Anniversary of NYS Agricultural Experiment Station - Geneva, 20 Aug 82 (Box 328, Folder 92)
  - Remarks - Student Convocation/Reception, 25 Aug 82 (Box 328, Folder 93)
  - Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation, 27 Aug 82 (Box 329, Folder 01)
  - Br. Remarks - Opening Sage Chapel Service, 29 Aug 82 (Box 329, Folder 02)
  - Speech - Opening Convocation - Hope College, 31 Aug 82 (Box 329, Folder 03)
  - Remarks - Dedication of the Biological Sciences Building, 09 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 4-5)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dinner in Honor of Mr. And Mrs. Dale R. Corson, 9 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 06)
  - Speech - Orientation of New Trustees - "Overview of Cornell", 14 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 07)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Orientation of New Members of the CUMC Board of Overseers, 15 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 08)
  - Remarks - Presidential Councillors Meeting - "State of the U.", 20 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 09)
  - Br. Remarks - Presidential Councillors Luncheon, 21 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 10)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Uris Library Addition, 21 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 11)
  - Br. Remarks - Development Real Estate Conference Luncheon, 24 Sep 82 (Box 329, Folder 12)
  - V. Br. Remarks - President's Reception for Parents' Weekend, 02 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 13)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dinner Honoring Mrs. Vincent Astor, 05 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 14)
  - Speech - Grossingers - "Education, Values and Society", 06 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 15-16)
  - Br. Remarks - Grumman Memorial Service, 07 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 17)
  - Speech - RPI Symposium - Industry-University-Government Cooperation, 12 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 18)
  - Br. Introduction - Hatfield Fellow - Clifton Garvin (Exxon), 14 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 19)
  - Br. Remarks - Dinner for Hatfield Fellow - Clifton Garvin, 14 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 20)
  - Br. Remarks - Law School Advisory Council, 15 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 21)
  - Br. Remarks - Geological Sciences Building Groundbreaking Ceremony, 21 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 22)
  - Speech - Trustee/Council Weekend - "State of the U", 22 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 23-24)
  - Br. Remarks - Luncheon for 50th Anniversary of Medical College Site, 25 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 25)
  - Br. Welcome and Introduce Main speaker - NYH/CUMC Capital Campaign Report, 25 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 26)
  - Speech - Cincinnati Alumni Dinner, 27 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 27)
  - Br. Remarks - Cincinnati Secondary Schools Reception, 27 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 27)
  - Br. Remarks - Memorial Service for Dean Solomon Hollister, 29 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 28)
  - Br. Remarks - Engineering Advisory council - Present Cornell Engineering Medal to Dudley Schoales, 29 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 29)
  - Br. Remarks - VIP Luncheon (Weiss Group), 30 Oct 82 (Box 329, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Luncheon - Stamford, CT, 05 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 31)
  - Br. Remarks - Secondary Schools/Admissions Reception - Stamford, CT, 05 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 32)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Stamford, CT (Fairfield County), 05 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 33)
  - Speech - University Assembly, 18 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 34)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Ken Wilson Dinner, 18 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 35)
  - Br. Remarks - VIP Reception, 19 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 36)
  - V. Br. Remarks - 150# Football Reception, 21 Nov 82 (Box 329, Folder 37)
  - Scripture Reading - Sage Chapel Christmas Program, 12 Dec 82 (Box 329, Folder 38)
  - Moderator (Br. Remarks) - University/Corporate Relations Meeting - University of Pennsylvania, 16 Dec 82 (Box 329, Folder 39)
  - Text for Annual Report, 04 Jan 83 (Box 329, Folder 40)
  - Br. Remarks - Academic Assembly of the Libraries, 11 Jan 83 (Box 329, Folder 41)
  - Speech - Commencement Address - University of the West Indies, 15 Jan 83 (Box 329, Folder 42)
  - Br. Introduction - Carl Sagan - Business and Higher Education Forum, 22 Jan 83 (Box 329, Folder 43)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Weiss, Peck & Greer Partners' Dinner, 29 Jan 83 (Box 329, Folder 44)
  - Br. Remarks (Issues) - FCR Meeting, 09 Feb 83 (Box 329, Folder 45)
  - Br. Introduction - Messenger Lecturer - Paul deMan, 14 Feb 83 (Box 329, Folder 46)
  - Br. Remarks - Ocean Club Luncheon - FL, 21 Feb 83 (Box 329, Folder 47)
  - Remarks (Statement) - House Budget Hearing - Washington, DC, 01 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 48)
  - Speech - Houston Geological and Geophysics Annual Meeting (Energy Speech), 07 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 49)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Donor Recognition Reception - Houston, 08 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 50)
  - Br. Welcome - Advisory Committee for the Center for Performing Arts, 24 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 51)
  - Br. Welcome - Trustees - Performing Arts Presentation, 25 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 52)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Funeral Service for Alfred M. Saperston, 30 Mar 83 (Box 329, Folder 53)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Employee Brown Bag Lunch, 03 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 54)
  - Br. Introduction - Messenger Lectures, 05 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 55)
  - Br. Remarks - Retirement Banquet for W. D. Cooke, 07 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 56)
  - Br. Welcome - Celtic Conference Banquet, 08 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 57)
  - Speech - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges - Atlanta, GA - "Public and Private Higher Education: A Costly Conflict", 11 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 58)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Meeting with Assemblies, 14 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 59)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Presentation of Performing Arts Center Architectural Drawings, 15 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 60)
  - Br. Introduction - Noyes Center 15th Anniversary Celebration, 16 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 61)
  - Speech - CU Law Alumni Luncheon - NYC, 22 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 62)
  - Br. Remarks - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 23 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 63)
  - Tower Club Dinner - NYC, 25 Apr 83 (Box 329, Folder 64)
  - Br. Welcome - Geological Conference on Cratonisation, -No Date- (Box 329, Folder 65)
  - Br. Remarks - Johnson Art Museum 10th Anniversary Celebration, 06 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 66)
  - Br. Remarks - Dinner with Berens' Group, 12 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 67)
  - V. Br. Remarks - VIP Reception, 13 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 68)
  - Speech - Law School Convocation, 22 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 69)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Commencement, 25 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 70)
  - Remarks - ROTC Commissioning Ceremony, 29 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 71)
  - Br. Introduction - Employee Brown Bag Lunch, 29 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 71)
  - Speech - Cornell Commencement, 29 May 83 (Box 329, Folder 72)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Thanks to Co-Chairs, Commencement Comm., Ushers Reception, 01 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 73)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Retiring Staff and Deans, 06 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 74)
  - Br. Remarks - Service Recognition Dinner, 07 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 75)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dinner at Johnson Art Museum - Olaf Brauner Exhibit, 08 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 76)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Million Dollar Class Ceremony, 10 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 77)
  - Br. Remarks - Reunion Forum Series, 10 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 77)
  - Br. Remarks - 50th Reunion Dinner, 10 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 77)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dedication of Tjaden Gallery, 10 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 77)
  - Remarks - CAA Annual Meeting (Report to Alumni), 11 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 78)
  - Br. Remarks - 25th Reunion Dinner, 11 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 78)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornelliana Night, 11 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 78)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Quarter Century Dinner, 14 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 79)
  - Br. Remarks - Meeting with UDC Representatives, 23 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 80)
  - Br. Remarks - Reception for Venezuela Cornell Alumni, 30 Jun 83 (Box 329, Folder 81)
  - Br. Remarks - Freshman Convocation, 24 Aug 83 (Box 329, Folder 82)
  - Br. Welcome - Sage Opening Service, 28 Aug 83 (Box 329, Folder 83)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Opening Exercises, 30 Aug 83 (Box 329, Folder 84)
  - Speech - Presidential Councillors - "State of the U.", 02 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 85)
  - Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation, 10 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 86)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Memorial Service for Jason Seeley, 12 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 87)
  - Br. Remarks - FCR Meeting, 14 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 88)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Meet with CU Football Team before CU/Penn Game, 17 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 89)
  - Br. Remarks - Meeting with Assemblies, 22 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 90)
  - Br. Welcome - Meet with Real Estate Group, 23 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 91)
  - Br. Welcome - Hall of Fame Banquet, 23 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 91)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Memorial Service for Kurt Hanslowe, 23 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 91)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Lake Professorship, 23 Sep 83 (Box 329, Folder 91)
  - V. Br. Remarks - President's Reception - Parents' Weekend, 01 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 92)
  - Br. Remarks - ACUSNY Annual Meeting, 04 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 93)
  - Remarks - CASE Volunteer of the Year Award - Robert Purcell, 05 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 94)
  - Br. Remarks - New Trustee Orientation, 06 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 95)
  - Speech - Trustee/Council Weekend - "State of the U.", 07 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 96)
  - Interview - Telra Film Crew - (Football Recruitment Film), 08 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 97)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Minority Fund Raising Event - Scarsdale, 09 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 98)
  - V. Br. Introduction - Messenger Lecturer, 10 Oct 83 (Box 329, Folder 99)
  - Br. Remarks - Sr. Staff Briefing - Lead Discussion re: Institutional Priorities and Objectives, 21 Oct 83 (Box 330, Folder 01)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Library Advisory Council Meeting, 21 Oct 83 (Box 330, Folder 01)
  - Br. Remarks - Half-time CU vs. Dartmouth, 22 Oct 83 (Box 330, Folder 02)
  - Br. Introduction - Hatfield Forum, 26 Oct 83 (Box 330, Folder 03)
  - Present Memento - Hatfield Forum Dinner, 26 Oct 83 (Box 330, Folder 03)
  - Speech - Missouri Public and Private Presidents Meeting, 07 Nov 83 (Box 330, Folder 04)
  - Br. Remarks - Tower Club Reception at Windows of the World - NYC, 14 Nov 83 (Box 330, Folder 05)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Student Phonathon Reception, 30 Nov 83 (Box 330, Folder 06)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Convocation at North Shore University Hospital, 04 Dec 83 (Box 330, Folder 07)
  - Reading - Sage Chapel Christmas Program, 11 Dec 83 (Box 330, Folder 08)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Memorial Service - Suh Young Hee/Erin Nieswand, 20 Dec 83 (Box 330, Folder 09)
  - Remarks - State of the U. - on the Sea Cloud, 20 Jan 84 (Box 330, Folder 10)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Performing Arts Reception - NYC, 27 Jan 84 (Box 330, Folder 11)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Weiss, Peck & Greer Partners' Dinner - NYC, 28 Jan 84 (Box 330, Folder 12)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Sr. Staff Briefing - Outlook for the Ivy League, 03 Feb 84 (Box 330, Folder 13)
  - Br. Remarks - Ocean Club Luncheon - FL, 20 Feb 84 (Box 330, Folder 14)
  - Br. Remarks - Vet College Faculty, 05 Mar 84 (Box 330, Folder 15)
  - Remarks - Meeting of the Association of Cornell Emeritus Professors, 15 Mar 84 (Box 330, Folder 16)
  - V. Br. Remarks - VIP Visit - Nutritional Sciences, 16 Mar 84 (Box 330, Folder 17)
  - Remarks - FR Comments at Board of Overseers, 21 Mar 84 (Box 330, Folder 18)
  - Speech - Harpur Forum - Binghamton - "The role of Liberal Arts in a Decade of Increased Technology", 29 Mar 84 (Box 330, Folder 19)
  - Speech - Student Honors Convocation - U. of Michigan - "Honors and What Else?", 01 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 20)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Washington, DC, 02 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 21)
  - Testify - House Subcommittee on Post Secondary Education - Wash., 04 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 22)
  - Br. Remarks - Human Ecology Advisory Council Meeting, 05 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 23)
  - Remarks - Entrepreneur of the Year Program, 06 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 24)
  - Welcome and Orientation - Corporate Liaison Committee, 10 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 25)
  - Speech - Alumni Dinner - Wilmington, Delaware, 13 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 26)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Robert Kesling's Retirement - U. of Michigan, 20 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 27)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Cornell Tradition Fellows' Tea, 24 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 28)
  - Br. Introduction - Hatfield Forum, 26 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 29)
  - Present Memento - Hatfield Forum Dinner, 26 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 29)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 28 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 30)
  - Br. Remarks - Tower Club Dinner, 30 Apr 84 (Box 330, Folder 31)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Engineering Convocation Luncheon, 04 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 32)
  - V. Br. Remarks - VIP Reception - Class of '60, 04 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 32)
  - Narrator - "Peter and the Wolf" - Risley Residential College Performance, 05 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 33)
  - Testify - House Science Committee - Washington, 08 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 34)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Meet with Joint Assemblies, 08 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 34)
  - V. Br. Welcome - Association of Black Admissions and Financial Aid Officers of Ivy and Sister Schools, 10 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 35)
  - V. Br. Remarks - VIP Reception - Athletics, 18 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 36)
  - Speech - LeMoyne College Commencement - "The Necessity of Commitment", 19 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 37)
  - B. Words of Response - Luncheon at LeMoyne College Commencement, 19 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 37)
  - Speech - Law School Convocation, 20 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 38)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Commencement, 22 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 39)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Luncheon for Presidential Scholars and Recognition of High School Teachers Program, 23 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 40)
  - Br. Welcome - New Employee Orientation, 24 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 41)
  - Br. Welcome - Reception for W. Keith Kennedy, 24 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 41)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dean Thomas's Retirement Dinner, 25 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 42)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Trustee Dinner Honoring Jansen Noyes, 26 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 43)
  - Remarks - Commissioning Ceremony, 27 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 44)
  - Br. Introduction - Baccalaureate Ceremony, 27 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 44)
  - Speech - Commencement, 27 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 45)
  - Moderator - ACUSNY Executive Committee Meeting - Rensselaerville, 30 May 84 (Box 330, Folder 46)
  - V. Br. Remarks - End-of-the-Year Barbecue for Executive staff, Deans and Spouses, 01 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 47)
  - Remarks - Dedication of DeFrees Laboratory, 04 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 48)
  - Br. Remarks - Employee Service Recognition Banquet, 05 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 49)
  - Welcome - Helmut Schmidt Luncheon, 08 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 50)
  - B. Welcome - Campaign Recognition Reception, 08 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 50)
  - Remarks - Class of '34 Dinner - 50th Reunion, 08 Jun 84 (Box 330, Folder 50)